opalconsultant.com 2010-05-07

# Privacy Policy

_**Privacy Policy Statement**_

Opal Consultant  does not sell, rent, or loan it's mailing list to any other organization or third parties. The   information you  provide, such as your address, e-mail address, and telephone number, is only used within   Opal Consultant to ensure  accurate and timely processing of orders. Everything is kept confidential and we will   remove any information concerning you  from our files at your request.  
  
**_Responses to Email Inquiries:_**

When visitors or members send email inquiries to our website, the return   email address  is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. We do not use the return email address for any  other purpose and do not  share the return email address with any third party. We may retain these emails for   our records, only for use as a  reference.   
  
**_Testimonials_** : 

If you submit a testimonial, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information   you   submit,  such as your name, website, e-mail ID or contact number may be displayed on our site, where it   could  potentially be used  by third parties to contact you, or send you unsolicited messages. We are not   responsible  for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in a testimonial. Although, as a   policy as of now,  in your personal interest we have  decided not to mention any personal information besides   your first name.  
  
**_How we use "cookies":_** __

A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit   certain web  sites. We may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical  purposes   to improve the  products and services we provide.   
If you are a visitor or member we may use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and   personalized  services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information.   Additionally, be aware that  if you visit other web sites where you are prompted to log in or that are   customizable, you may be required to accept  cookies.  
Advertisers on our website may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and   expressly disclaim  responsibility for information collected through them.

**_Online Shopping_ :**

At some web sites described within our product, you can purchase products and services or   register to  receive materials, such as a newsletter. You can decide whether or not to use these sites or   services at your own discretion.  
  
**_Legal:_**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when   we believe  that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court   order, or legal process  served on our web site. 

E-mail: [ _Query@opalconsultant_](mailto:query@opalconsultant.com?subject=Query).com __
